Some rules should never be broken.
A Sound of Thunder is a thriller, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Peter Hyams.
When a hunter sent back to the prehistoric era runs off the path he must not leave,
he causes a chain reaction that alters history in disastrous ways.
Travis Ryer, played by Edward Burns.
Sonia Rand, played by Catherine McCormack.
Charles Hatton, played by Ben Kingsley.
Ted Eckles, played by William Armstrong.
Jenny Krase, played by Jemima Rooper.
Marcus Payne, played by David Oyelowo.
A Sound of Thunder is a 2005 science fiction
thriller film directed by Peter Hyams.
It is based on the 1952 short story of the same name by Ray Bradbury.
The film stars Edward Burns, Catherine McCormack, and Ben Kingsley.
It follows "time tourists" who accidentally interfere too much
with the past, completely altering the present.
A Sound of Thunder was released in the United States
on September 2, 2005, by Warner Bros.
The film failed at the box office, earning only $11.8 million against a production budget of $80 million, and was largely panned by critics, who criticized
its cheap special effects, uninvolved performances, scientific errors and choppy logic, and the lack of faithfulness to the source material.
The film explores themes of dying and death,
future, hunter, technology, time travel.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.